

# JD HAMDALLA



Rancho Cucamonga, CA 91730 (909) 204-1258 majdhamdallah42@gmail.com

# **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Skilled Labor Worker with strong track record of success in maintenance, repair and general labor. Multitasks and works well in fast-paced, high-volume environments. Flexible work and shift schedule with expertise operating basic hand and power tools. Excellent work performance in individual and team roles combined with superior attendance record.

## ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Used Microsoft Excel to develop inventory tracking spreadsheets.
- Supervised team of staff members.
- Resolved product issue through consumer testing.

#### **SKILLS**

- Night Auditing
- Reading Comprehension
- **Budget Implementation**
- Money Handling

#### Training Methods

- Conflict Management
- Guest Experience Management

## **WORK HISTORY**

#### **DIRECTOR OF CLIENT RELATIONS**

08/2015 to CURRENT

#### Highlander Auditorium | Upland, CA

- Accommodate all guests at high school events to seating and any special needs assistance
- Answer any guest inquiries and provide excellent sources of help for guests
- Prepare and set-up stage, seating, and audio technology for performances and shows (including lifting and transporting heavy equipment)
- Maintained high employee satisfaction and performance with hands-on and collaborative style
- Managed six staff members to deliver timely and courteous guest service in front desk, housekeeping and maintenance operations

### **CURATIVE CLINICAL LAB ASSISTANT**

08/2020 to 03/2022

#### Curative Inc. | San Dimas, CA

- Assisting CLS', Lab Technicians Lab Accessioning and Plating teams (as needed)
- Checking inventory and ordering supplies
- Performing clerical duties
- Demonstrated proficiency in computer skills, such as word processing and laboratory information
- Strong understanding of good laboratory practices and regulatory compliance
- Other duties as assigned., Help podiatrist in locating and providing medical tools to provide to patients
- Maintaining and updating patient files while ensuring HIPAA compliance
- Observed roles within clinic while staff interacted with patients and provided treatments
- Documented and verified patient information using laboratory information system.
- Kept supplies organized and well-stocked, requesting more supplies and avoiding unnecessary testing delays.

## **CASHIER AND SERVER**

09/2017 to 08/2020

## Blue Fin Sushi and Teriyaki

- Ensure pleasant dining experience for all customers of varying backgrounds by displaying excellent customer service, knowledge of items and preparation methods.
- Train new staff on company protocols and procedures to provide quality customer service
- Collect payment for orders and occasionally deliver orders locally to customers
- Greeted customers entering store and responded promptly to customer needs.
- Built relationships with customers to encourage repeat business.

# **EDUCATION**

**B.S** | Political Science

EXPECTED IN 12/2023

California State University, Long Beach, CA

Chaffey College, Rancho Cucamonga, CA

Associate of Science | Political Science

08/2017

**CERTIFICATIONS** 

Coding Certificate UCLA (February 2024) Regional Occupational Program 2014, Certificate of Completion in Nursing June 2015

**LANGUAGES** 

Arabic

Professional Working